

#### MASTER STUDENT · COMPUTER VISION · MEDICAL IMAGE PROCESSING

4259 Nagatsuta-cho, Midori-ku Yokohama, Kanagawa 226-8503 Japan

□ (+81) 090-9102-7626 | SunHaozju@outlook.com | Ahaosun99.xyz | OsunHao-TokyoTech | Inhaosun117/

"Keep stupid, keep hungry."

Su	m	m	a	r۱	V
$\mathbf{v}$			ч		v

I am currently a master student at Tokyo Institute of Technology, supervised by Prof. Kenji SUZUKI. I received my B.Eng degree from the School of Computer Science and Technology, Zhejiang University in 2021. At that time, I am also a member of Chu Kochen Honors College. During the university, I also minored in Religious Philosophy, Zhejiang University. Now my main research interest lies in medical image processing, dose reduction for CT.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

### Fenlai Intelligent Co.,Ltd.

ShenZhen, China

COMPUTER VISION ALGORITHM ENGINEER (INTERNSHIP)

Mar.2021 - Jun.2021

- Smart gym based on computer vision technology. I am responsible for the overall architecture design and algorithm implementation of the group exercise project, and realize the multi-person real-time group exercise scoring and action correction system.
- Edge deployment of deep learning models and load balancing system.

Hikvision Co.,Ltd. HangZhou, China

COMPUTER VISION ALGORITHM ENGINEER (INTERNSHIP)

Sep.2021 - Oct.2021

• Investigate video-based pedestrian re-identification technology.

### Honors & Awards

#### INTERNATIONAL

2022 IIR Research Fellow, Institute of Innovative Research (IIR), Tokyo Institute of Technology

Tokyo, Japan

#### **DOMESTIC**

2018 **2rd Scholarship**, Zhejiang University

HangZhou, China

### Presentation

•

## Publications \_\_\_\_\_

•

### Education \_\_\_\_\_

#### **ZheJiang University**

HangZhou, China

B.ENG IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep. 2017 - Jul.2021

• Selected as a member of Chu Kochen Honors College and won the 2rd scholarship of Zhejiang University.

### **Tokyo Institute of Technology**

Tokyo, Japan

M.ENG IN INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

Sep. 2021 - Jul.2023

Research Fellow from Institute of Innovative Research(IIR)

JULY 28, 2022 HAO SUN · RÉSUMÉ 1